Being busy is so much better than being
expensive.
That's what we're working towards,
but we need that golden elixir of demand.
You want to make sure you've got enough
people on your books that if a few drop
out, you can replace them, and
that you're in the trenches understanding
people's
problems.
Because if you're working with more
clients, you're getting more problems
in front of you,
which give you great ideas for content,
whether it's YouTube,
Instagram, TikTok, Facebook,
YouTube Shorts, whatever it is.
Content, data, landing pages,
sales process,
and automating it makes it way
better. Just briefly,
if you do sales calls, people book in,
they see
that your times are all open, they bounce,
or you're busy, they
bounce. You're in a different time zone,
they bounce.
They don't show up, that annoys you.
They don't buy, that annoys you.
And you don't want to be deflated with the
efforts of your business.
And if people-- This
is the best thing for me,
from a mental health perspective.
Nine out of 10 people could visit--
Or do you know what?
99 out of 100 people could leave my
landing page and go, "Fuck this,
I'm out." I
don't know about it. All I know
is the people that come in through the
door, and
I'm thinking,
"What a great business I run.
I'm getting five new clients today."
If I jump on a sales call and I'm spending
hours in front of people
and they're going, "Yeah, sounds great,
James, but no,
thanks." [groans] I get depressed. No,
I'm joking.
Long and short of the story,
if you can work on those,
you can do amazing.